<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Benalmadena</string>
    <string name="osa_adress">• AVD GAMONAL 7 PARKING OPPOSITE AGUILA APPARTAMENT \n• AVD. ANTONIO MACHADO 56 LOCAL 5 \n• AVD. GAMONAL 11 NUEVA PLAZA BONANZA ESC 1 LOCAL 4</string>

    <string name="belgien_corner_1"><b>HALF PRICE AT JUST 2.50€!</b> (Normally 5€)</string>
    <string name="flamenco">Flamenco Benalmadena awarded a Certificate of Excellence. Due to good performance in delivering the best flamenco in Benalmadena and Costa del Sol in general. It has also been attracting a huge number of people.</string>


    <string name="flamenco1">Come and join us on Friday for a fun wine tasting followed by our famous Gypsy Kings tribute show with the delightful Jaime accompanied by our guitarist! \n\nTickets cost 15 euros and include a tasting of 3 Spanish wines plus a free glass of wine to enjoy with the show, perhaps accompanied by a tapa of delicious cheese or ham. We are child-friendly, and there’s also the chance to learn a few dance steps. \n<i>A Limited number of tickets available.</i></string>

    <string name="flamenco2">Flamenco Benalmádena is the perfect setting to experience unique and authentic flamenco! Our artists have been professionally trained in the Andalusian city of Seville, the birthplace of flamenco. They have now brought their skill and passion to the heart of the Costa del Sol to offer unmissable performances for tourists and local residents alike. \n\n<b>Flamenco Benalmádena is delighted to offer "Flamenco Tradicional”, our signature traditional flamenco performance.</b>\n\nThe show lasts over an hour and features between three and four artists. It is performed in a traditional way that is unique every time and different to other shows on offer elsewhere, ensuring an unforgettable experience. Buy tickets before and get a special offer : A free drink \n<b>Date: Saturday at 8 pm</b>\n<b>Price: 15 euros</b>\n<i>A Limited number of tickets because we want to take care of traditional flamenco.</i>\n\n<b>Private events, weddings and flamenco classes</b>\nWe are also available for organised events, you can hire our able services to spread out the cheer, class and glamour to those in attendance. Do you have a group of people you would like to entertain any other day apart from Saturday? Then you are sorted out, we are available for any private events.
</string>


    <string name="art_hair"><b>OFFER 1.</b>\n(lavar y peinar) labio superior gratis. \n(depilación con el hilo o cera) \n<b>(Wash and blow dry)</b> \nMoustache free with cord or wax. \n\n<b>OFFER 2.</b> \n(tinte y lavar y peinar) labio superior y la ceja gratis. \n(a elegir con la cera o el hilo) \n<b>(colour and wash and blow dry)</b> \nmoustache and eyebrows free (wax or string). \n\n<b>OFFER 3.</b> \n(Tinte y corte y peinar) la ceja y el rostro con el hilo gratis. \n<b>(colour and cut and blow dry)</b> \nEyebrows and full face with wax or string.</string>

    <string name="la_fista">Welcome to La Fiesta, Bar and Tapas Cafe in the heart of Benalmadena, located just down from Hotel Bali. \n\nYou\'re ensured a warm welcome with live sky sports, fantastic tapas dishes and brilliant cocktails as well as a great selection of beers, wines and spirits. </string>

    <string name="the_salon">Hi I\'m Jesse originally from Bristol. I\'ve been barbering since I was 16 years old. I would like to offer a discount to all Benalmadena residents. Haircut normally 12€ - but for residents who mention Discover Benalmadena ONLY 10€. \n\nI also do a great facial steam cleanse and cut throat shave, so if you want to look and feel amazing but at a really competitive price give The Salon a call for the ultimate male grooming experience.</string>

    <string name="history_benal">In the beginning God created Benalmadena! Well not quite, but Benalmadena and the surrounding area has had a long and checkered past. \n\nIn the 7th century BC, the Phoenicians arrived followed by the Romans in the early part of the 8th century AD. But the name Benalmadena came from the Moors who arrived later in the 8th century. The original name wa Ben-Al-Madina, which in Arabic translated as "children of the mines". At that time there were many iron ore and ochre mines in the area. \n\nThe 14th century saw the population diminish due to the many coastal attacks by the infamous Barbary pirates. In 1485 the Moorish Benalmadena castle was destroyed by the Christian armies. The castle stood on the site now occupied by by the Santa Domingo church in Benalmadena Pueblo. The church was originally constructed in the 17th century. \n\n Benalmadena became an important defence from seaboune raids in the 15th century, and was known as Vigia de la Costa, or "lookout for the coast". The towns coat of arms still portrays this today. Three look out towers were built, (torres), and the remains can still be seen. One is situated in Benalmadena Costa, near the marina, and is called Torre Bermeja. The other two are at Torrequebrada and Torremuelle respectively. \n\Probably the worst disaster the area had seen happened in 1680 when an earthquake occurred. No houses were left standing and the fishing boats were destroyed by the following tsunami.
 \n\nIn the late 18th century, the population started to recover when an Italian named Felix Solesio opened paper mills in the area of Arroyo de la Miel in 1784. The ruins of one of these can be seen today in Plaza Tribuna, which is adjacent to Plaza Espana in Arroyo. This lasted for around thirty years until Felix Solesio became bankrupt. The next phase was the cultivation of Muscatel grapes which lasted until the late 1800s, when the Phylloxera epidemic struck and ruined all the vines. \n\nWe then come to the early 1960s when the package holiday tourists started to arrive on the Costa del Sol by the planeload from northern Europe. The La Roca was the first hotel built in the town but was quickly followed by many more. In 1972 work started on the construction of the marina, and Tivoli World theme park opened in 1973. The marina opened in 1982 followed by Paloma Park in the late 1980s. \n\n<i>Reproduced with kind permission from benalmadena-arroyo.com</i></string>

    <string name="banal_costa"><b>Home to the majority of the main attractions of which the first to mention should probably be the beautiful sandy beaches and the deep blue Mediterranean Sea. </b> \n\nA wide range of restaurants and bars to suit all tastes and budgets can be found in abundance and the area has a relaxed and very family friendly vibe all year round. \n\nAnother of the main attractions to be found in Benalmadena Costa is the wonderful Puerto Marina. The marina is a great spot for Shopping and eating out as well as looking at the luxury yachts and celebrity spotting.</string>

    <string name="banal_costa1">The marina also plays host to the Sea Life Centre to get up close and personal to our friends in the sea.</string>

    <string name="banal_costa2">La Paloma Park is also worthy of a mention right in the centre of Benalmadena Costa. The Park is beautifully set out with landscaped gardens and waterfalls which all run down to the main lake. With a wonderful array of animals and exotic birds this truly is a must visit attraction. \n\nBeside the park you will find Selwo Marina where you can get up close to Dolphins, Sea Lions, Crocodiles and much more</string>

    <string name="arroyo"><b>Arroyo de la Miel is the central town that links Benalmadena Pueblo to the Costa. Arroyo is a thriving hub and a great area for Shopping and Eating. The train station can be found here which links the town all along the coast from Malaga to Fuengirola.</b> \n\nOne of the main attractions in Arroyo is the Cable Car which takes you to the top of the mountain so you can enjoy a mesmorising panoramic view of the the area both inland and out to sea. North Africa can be seen on clear days.</string>

    <string name="arroyo1">As you come out of the cable car station you will find another of Arroyo’s attractions Tivoli World which offers family thrill seeking fun set in beautiful gardens with illuminated fountains and even its own currency. On a Friday the Car Park at Tivoli World hosts the main market.</string>
    <string name="banal_pueblo"><b>The Pueblo is the original village and still maintains its Spanish charm. With beautiful whitewashed buildings and flowers and a abundance of alleys and traditional squares.</b> \n\nPlaza Espana is the main square in the Pueblo and is home to La Nina who has become the symbol of Benalmadena. Other attractions to note here are the beautiful Colomares Castle</string>
    <string name="banal_pueblo1">which also boasts the worlds smallest chapel, The Benalmadena Stupa which is the largest monument of it’s kind in Europe and has amazing views over the coast. Entrance to the Stupa is free. </string>
    <string name="banal_pueblo2">Also worth a visit is the Butterfly park which has around 1600 butterflies in a tropicalized environment and is also the largest of its kind in Europe.</string>

    <string name="aqualand">What a day out! The biggest water park on the Coast del Sol is a family-focused water park with lots of slides, rapids &amp; a surf beach area with wave machine and doesn\'t disappoint!</string>

    <string name="aqualand1">Fun for all the family is guaranteed with faster rides for the teens and big kids such as Boomarang! Anaconda and Twister and more leisurely rides and areas like Laguna Tropical and Children\'s Paradise with the ever popular Surf Beach including wave machine and sun beds.</string>
    <string name="transport">Getting around the local area couldn\'t be easier with the local public transport letting you get out and see attractions further afield without the hassle and expense of a hire car.</string>
    <string name="transport1">There are frequent buses to and from Benalmadena with cheaper than UK fares which can also be booked online.</string>
    <string name="transport2">Trains are a great way to get around the local area, again with cheaper than UK fares, air-con, plus announcements and signage in English as well as Spanish.</string>
    <string name="eat_out_1">In Benalmadena, you will discover a vast array of restaurants, many of which are located in and around the Marina which is a hub of nightlife and gastronomy. The town and beach front offers everything from traditional Spanish tapas bars to luxury fine-dining restaurants and an opportunity to ‘eat your way around the world’ - with all types of international cuisine on offer for both visitors and locals people alike.</string>
    <string name="la_nina">At La Niña del Guardia restaurant we serve Spanish and international food. We have tapas such as; Russian salad, meatballs, chicken on skewers, prawns on skewers, and special dishes like rabbit with mustard sauce, chicken in prawn sauce, pork loin with malaga wine, plus fantastic salads, Iberian products, wines and much more. </string>
    <string name="la_nina1">We are now open in the afternoon for drinks and snacks, including our special ALL DAY Cognac + Coffee + Cake offer (our cakes are delicious!) With a HAPPY HOUR from 16.30 – 19.30. \n\nThe restaurant environment is very cozy and designed to be very comfortable and family orientated too.</string>
    <string name="la_nina2">We are based in the heart of Arroyo de la Miel: Avenida de la Constitución 35 (in front of the playground). The nearest bus stop is about ten meters away and from the train station simply follow the avenue in a straight line. \n\nWe will be happy to welcome you very soon and we assure you that you will not forget us!</string>
    <string name="el_club_nautico">Our beautiful restaurant is set on the edge of Peurto Marina with amazing views across the marina and the ocean beyond. We serve delicious locally sourced food with a Scandinavian-Spanish fusion including lunch and dinner including an A La Carte menu in our restaurant, bistro and terrace with our Cantina down by the dock.
</string>

    <string name="el_club_nautico1">• Sea Front Restaurant \n\n• Lounge \n\n• Cocktail Bar \n\n• Private Events\n</string>

    <string name="el_club_nautico2">Our professional service with over 15 years experience in event management will work to design and produce your special event ensuring the highest level of service and quality.\n\nIt can be a cocktail party, a family event, product launch, press conference, business breakfast or a gala dinner…Anything is possible \n\n <i>We work together with you to make your event work just as your dreamed of.</i></string>
    <string name="tobarna">Located in the town of Torremolinos the Pepe López Taberna Flamenca has offered the best traditional flamenco show Costa del Sol for over 50 years. \n\nLet yourself go in the hands of our 10 artists flamenco and classical Spanish culture. \n\nOpen most evenings, please see our website for up to date show times and to book.</string>
    <string name="capon1">We offer a very warm welcome and a chance for you to sing your heart out whist enjoying our extensive selection of drinks. Look out for our drinks promotions too! </string>
    <string name="capon2">Regular live entertainment from top acts and themed events take place throughout the year. Keep an eye on our Facebook page for all the latest news. \n\n<b>Come and unleash your inner talent and shine like a star whilst enjoying a brilliant night out at Capone’s. We guarantee you will keep coming back for more!</b></string>
    <string name="here_at_last">We serve breakfast, lunch, dinner, drinks and coffee. \n\nExample dishes:\nFish and Chips only 6€\nSteaks from 8€\nPork chops from 5.50€\nSteak burgers from 5€\nHomeMade Chips 2.50€ a portion!</string>
    <string name="night_life">Benalmadena is a fun, thriving and lively resort that can boast a huge number of late night bars, nightclubs and karaoke venues to suit all budgets and most tastes in music. \n\nBenalmadena is a fun, thriving and lively resort that can boast a huge number of late night bars, nightclubs and karaoke venues to suit all budgets and most tastes in music.</string>
    <string name="shopping_in">There is a good opportunity to ‘shop until you drop’ in Benalmadena with plenty of choice including a good number if independent businesses offering a variety of goods. The main shopping location is the central town area of Arroyo de la Meil and the Marina although there are plenty of excellent businesses scattered throughout the town and part of the fun is discovering them!</string>
    <string name="shop">Find us at:<b> The Vape Station @ Drew\'s Place</b></string>
    <string name="air_con">• Fixing\n• Installations\n• Repairs\n• Servicing\n• Advice &amp; Help</string>
    <string name="tv_1">• Set Top Boxes\n• IPTV Services\n• UK &amp; European TV\n• Worldwide Sport\n• Advice &amp; Help</string>
    <string name="tv_2">• Set Top Boxes\n• Accessories\n• Advice &amp; Help\n• Re-sellers Required</string>
    <string name="living_benal">Benalmadena is a wonderful place to live, with an average annual temperature in excess of 22 degrees and conveniently located just 15 minutes from Malaga airport. This means that the rest of the world is effectively on it’s doorstep. The area also has one of the largest ex-pat residencies on the Costa Del Sol so there is a real community spirit.\n\nThere are plenty of attractions in the area for all ages making Benalmadena a great place to live all year round. These include the cable car with stunning views, theme parks, Andalucía’s largest Marina plus a lovely leafy green park on the doorstep not to mention the beautiful golden sandy beaches. The Marina itself has a very cosmopolitan feel.</string>
    <string name="living_benal1">The main tourist spots are all very popular, but there are plenty of little villages and quiet places to discover away from the crowds, all just a short drive or bus ride away.\n\nRecent regeneration in the area has seen investments made in local infrastructure, not least the state-of-the-art  Xanit Hospital which provides the best in health care on the Costa del Sol.</string>
    <string name="living_benal2">Property prices here range from €50,000 for a typical 1 bedroom apartment to €400,000 upwards for country fincas. There is a great choice of property in all price ranges with beachside apartments and inland villas dominating the property scene in this area. Benalmadena offers truly outstanding value both in the sales and rental market when compared to the UK.</string>
    <string name="de_casa">If you want advice on the best properties in Benalmadena then Trevor and Wendy Johnson of De Costa Properties are the people you need to see.\n\nAfter getting off the bus at the \'wrong stop\' in the 70\'s and falling in love with the 500 year old Benalmadena Pueblo they moved here in 1984 and have lived and worked here ever since.\n\nDe Costa Properties specialises in property within the Pueblo and a 1km radius in all directions as well as working together with other agents along the coast.\n\nDespite the recent uncertainty of Brexit the village continues to be a magnet for many Nationalities including Danish, Finnish, Norwegians and, of course, the British\n\nWhile tourism in Greece, Turkey, and Tunisia look less and less appealing, millions of tourists will come to Spain this summer and Benalmadena village is definitely one for their must-visit list!
</string>
    <string name="de_case_1">Set in large lawned gardens with the largest pool in the area plus childrens pool, this spacious apartment with three bedrooms and two bathrooms is conveniently located close to the old Village of Benalmadena Pueblo and all of its facilities. The property has private car parking and garage storeroom.There is a modern fully equipped kitchen opening to an interior patio serving as a laundry room and family BBQ area, to the South with sea views over the garden is the main terrace along the length of the property furnished with table chairs &amp; sun loungers.\nDistance to the airport is 17 km and the nearest beach is less than 5 minutes.\n\nRef: 2841. Price: €180,000</string>
    <string name="de_case_2">A well maintained single level Villa on an enclosed and private plot which is absolutely flat with extensive lawns, flowering shrubs and a maginficent Palm tree as a centrepoint. The views across the Mediterranean over Fuengirola in the distance are really quite spectacular &amp; the property is not overlooked.All bathrooms have been recently reformed and the kitchen and equipmentrenewed to an extremely high standard. A feature of the house is the raised surrounding terrace which is comfortably furnished for relaxing and outdoor dining, an ideal location to take advantage of the open views. Close to shops, S\'mkts, restuarants and bars, 20 minutes to the airport.\n\nRef: 2839. Price: €660,000</string>
    <string name="de_case_3">A really cute semi detached Villa with lots of nice facilities and in really excellent
decorative order. There is a prívate garden with pool and sea views from terrace.
There are a total of 3 bedrooms and two bathrooms which due to the two level
design is distrubuted with accommodation as follows:-
On the entry level are two bedrooms and bathroom, a very well designed kitchen
with all of the required domestic appliances and a spacious salón with fireplace.
Underneath and at garden level is an independant apartment with access direct
to the garden with bedroom/ sitting room, bathroom and a further kitchen.
From the cul de sac lane with parking, there is parking inside the gate for one car.
We have additional photographs to send by Email on request \n\Ref: 2784. Price: €299,000</string>
    <string name="casa_1">Casa Annabel sister Casa Christabel are set in the beautifully landscaped and tranquil Mi Jardin, which has the atmosphere of a Spanish pueblo and was carefully constructed in a traditional Andalusian style.</string>
    <string name="casa_2">Casa Christabel is an air conditioned and heated one bed apartment with two singles which can also be made up as a King size. The comfortable sofa bed in the living area easily sleeps two extra adults.\n\nCasa Annabel is an air conditioned and heated studio with a king sized bed and a day bed which can be made up as a single or a double for two extra adults.</string>
    <string name="casa_3">There is free UK TV and Wifi. A cot and high chair are also available.\n\nThe well equipped kitchens allow for easy self catering or if staying in Casa Christabel why not have a relaxed meal from the barbecue.</string>
    <string name="casa4">The beautiful blue flag Carvajal beach with is highly recommended Chiringuito\'s is an easy 15 minute walk downhill ( 20 on the way back). Treat yourself to a swim in the lovely pool which is a 3 minute walk through the gardens from the apartments.\n\nThe shops, bars and pavement cafes are a 20 minute walk and there is even an Aldi a further 5 minutes walk.\n\nThe Carvajal train station is a 20 minute walk giving easy access to Benalmadena, Fuengirola, Malaga city and the airport.\n\nBenalmadena has an award winning marina, and many tourist attractions such as Tivoli world, Selwo Marina and Selwoo Aventura, and is famous for its night life.\n\nFuengirola also has a marina, beach front promenade with upmarket tapas bars and restaurants and boutique shops.\n\nMalaga city itself is also well worth a visit, famous for its art culture and gastronomy..\n\nThe journey to airport takes just under 30 minutes and costs around 2 Euros. The station is inside the airport terminal however the trains stop running from 2330 to 0530.\n\nA car is therefore not really necessary although it would be an advantage if you like to explore. Free communal parking is available</string>
    <string name="casa5">There are steps down to the apartments so they may not be suitable for those with walking difficulties.\n\nCasa Christabel is adjoining Casa Annabel and both apartments may be booked together for larger groups of families or friends.\n\nGuests may check in at any time that suits them after 1600 as there is a locked key box. I do not require a set check in day. Check out is by 1200.\n\nBoth apartments are available for longer lets at reduced prices during the winter months.\n\nPrices quoted are for two people. Additional people are charged at £5 per person per night for a maximum of two extra people, or 4 people if booking both Casa Christabel and Casa Annabel.\n\nDeposit of 50% paid at time of booking and the remainder 60 days prior to check in, plus a returnable damage deposit of £250 per apartment. This will be repaid 72 hours following check out provided no damage or loss is reported.</string>
    <string name="casa_ch">Casa Christabel and sister Casa Annabel are set in the beautifully landscaped and tranquil Mi Jardin, which has the atmosphere of a Spanish pueblo and was carefully constructed in a traditional Andalusian style.</string>

    <string name="casa_ch1">Casa Christabel is an air conditioned and heated one bed apartment with two singles which can also be made up as a King size. The comfortable sofa bed in the living area easily sleeps two extra adults.\n\nCasa Annabel is an air conditioned and heated studio with a king sized bed and a day bed which can be made up as a single or a double for two extra adults.</string>
    <string name="hair_beauty">We are a Hair and Beauty salon established for over 6 years in Benalmadena Pueblo\n\nThe Salon is one of the only hair salons in Spain that is registered with the British Hair Council and Dennis and his team of highly experienced staff carry with them a wealth of knowledge and expertise in the industry using milkshake and CND Products.\n\nIf you want to look amazing but at a really competitive price give The Salon a call for the ultimate pamper experience.\n</string>
    <string name="car_hire">Hiring a car in Benalmadena gives you quick access to all that the area can offer both centrally and on the outskirts. Whether you are seeking a secluded beach space, wanting to take in the view from the Pueblo or discovering the delights of the wider Costa Del Sol, then hiring a car can help you achieve this conveniently. \n\nMalaga Airport is only a 15 minute drive away, giving you a plethora of hire options, dependent on your needs and what your budget is. The best will offer a ‘meet and greet’ service but most companies in the area are based in and around the airport.</string>
    <string name="wedding">Getting married in or around Benalmadena or within the wider Costa Del Sol is a dream for many couples.\n\nThe warm climate, friendly hospitality, gorgeous wedding venues in stunning locations, easy access and of course fantastic value for money make a wedding in Benalmadena a perfect option.</string>
    <string name="golf">Golf is naturally one of the most popular sports on the Costa del Sol, and something which attracts hundreds of thousands of tourists to the area every year.\n\nGolf courses in Benalmadena are challenging yet fun for even the least experienced of golfers. Play a fantastic 18 holes in the beautiful sun during the day and experience the best nightlife on the Costa del Sol at night.</string>
    <string name="pharmacies">There are many pharmacies (farmacia) in the Belmadena area and they can help you with a wide variety of minor ailments from sunburn treatment and mosquito repellant to treating infections with antibiotics that you would have to see a doctor about first in the UK. \n\nNearly all medicines in Spain have to be purchased from a pharmacy, even things like Paracetemol that you would buy from a supermarket in the UK. \n\nThey are easy to spot with the neon green flashing cross being displayed outside or within a window and take it in turns to open throughout the night and across holidays.</string>
    <string name="dentist">If you need emergency dental treatment while in Benalmadena you can go to the hospital where they usually have a dentist on hand to cater for emergencies. Your European Health Insurance Card will give you a reduced cost or free treatment from the state healthcare provider but it is advisable to check your travel insurance covers dental. </string>
    <string name="medical"><b>Hospital de Alta Resolución</b>\nOpen from 08:00 - 20:00 Mon - Fri\nThe clinic accepts patients living or staying in the postcode area 29631 and others.\nCL MERCURIO, URB. PUEBLOSOL, s/n\nARROYO DE LA MIEL-BENALMADENA\nTel: 951 920 720</string>
    <string name="medical1"><b>Arroyo de la Miel Clinic</b>\nOpen 24 hours.The hospital accepts patients from all parts of Benalmadena.\nAVDA. DEL ARROYO HONDO, s/n\nARROYO DE LA MIEL-BENALMADENA\nTel: 951 976 000\nEmergencies: 902 505 061</string>
    <string name="medical2"><b>Torrequebrada Clinic</b>\nOpen from 08:00 - 20:00 Mon - Fri\nThe clinic accepts patients living or staying in the postcode area 29630\nwhich is where most of the hotels and apartments are situated.\nCL SOL, TORREQUEBRADA\nTel: 951 308 120</string>
    <string name="medical3"><b>Other Local Facilities</b>\n\n<b>Hospitals:</b>\nMarbella Costa Del Sol – Tel: +34 952 828 250\nBenalmadena Chare – Tel: + 34 951 976 000\nCarlos De Haya – Tel: +34 951 290 000\nChip Hospital (private) - Tel: +34 951 011 150\nClinic Malaga University – Tel: +34 951 032 000\nXanit – Tel: +34 952 367 190\n\n<b>Heath Centres:</b>\nCentral De Salud\nTorrequebrada, Benalmadena – Tel: +34 951 308 120\nArroyo De La Miel – Tel: +34 951 920 720\nCalle San Miguel, Torremolinos – Tel: + 34 951 924 100\nLa Carihuela, Torremolinos – Tel: + 34 951 920 920\nSalud Responde (General Call Centre) Will Direct you to all – Tel: +34 902 505 060\n</string>
    <string name="police">Calling the Police in Spain: <b>092</b>\n\nFor the national Police dial: <b>091</b>\n\nNational emergency number dial: <b>112</b>\n\n<i>Most Spanish emergency services will not speak English so it\'s probably best to find a Spanish speaker to call if possible.</i></string>
    <string name="police_1">1. Call the national police\n2. Explain the incident and that you need a police report\n3. Go to your nearest police station and collect the report\n4. present the police report to your insurance company on your return</string>
    <string name="ambulance">For an ambulance in Spain dial: <b>080</b>\n\nNational emergency number dial:<b>112</b>\n\n<i>Most Spanish emergency services will not speak English so it\'s probably best to find a Spanish speaker to call if possible.</i></string>
    <string name="emergency">All emergencies you can dial: <b>112</b>\n\n<i>Most Spanish emergency services will not speak English so it\'s probably best to find a Spanish speaker to call if possible.
</i></string>
    <string name="texi">Radio Taxi Benalmadena <b>(+34) 952 44 15 45</b>\n\nTaxiBenalmadena.es <b>(+34) 690 25 18 25</b>\n\nMalaga Transfers <b>(+34) 679 21 66 71</b></string>
    <string name="dutyfree"><i>Although there are no limits on the amount of alcohol and tobacco you can purchase to take home if you are in the EU, customs are more likely to query your purchase if you go over the recommended limit.</i></string>
    <string name="dutyfree1">• 800 Cigarettes\n• 400 Cigarillos\n• 200 Cigars\n• 1kg of Smoking Tobacco\n\n• 100 Litres of Beer\n• 10 Litres of Spirits\n• 90 Litres of Wine\n• 20 Litres of Fortified Wine (eg. Port or Sherry) </string>



</resources>
